[
{"Front": "あ", "Back": "Ah", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ああ", "Back": "like that", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あいさつ・する", "Back": "to greet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "間", "Back": "a space", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "合う", "Back": "to match", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あかちゃん", "Back": "infant", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "上る", "Back": "to rise", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "赤ん坊", "Back": "baby", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "空く", "Back": "to open, to become empty", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "アクセサリー", "Back": "accessory", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あげる", "Back": "to give", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "浅い", "Back": "shallow,superficial", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "味", "Back": "flavour", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "アジア", "Back": "Asia", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "明日", "Back": "tomorrow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "遊び", "Back": "play", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "集る", "Back": "to gather", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "集める", "Back": "to collect something", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "アナウンサー", "Back": "announcer", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "アフリカ", "Back": "Africa", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "アメリカ", "Back": "America", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "謝る", "Back": "to apologize", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "アルコール", "Back": "alcohol", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "アルバイト", "Back": "part-time job", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "安心", "Back": "relief", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "安全", "Back": "safety", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あんな", "Back": "such", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "案内", "Back": "to guide", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "以下", "Back": "less than", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "以外", "Back": "with the exception of", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "医学", "Back": "medical science", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "生きる", "Back": "to live", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "意見", "Back": "opinion", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "石", "Back": "stone", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いじめる", "Back": "to tease", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "以上", "Back": "more than,this is all", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "急ぐ", "Back": "to hurry", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "致す", "Back": "(humble) to do", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いただく", "Back": "(humble) to receive", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一度", "Back": "once", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一生懸命", "Back": "with utmost effort", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いっぱい", "Back": "full", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "糸", "Back": "thread", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "以内", "Back": "within", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "田舎", "Back": "countryside", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "祈る", "Back": "to pray", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いらっしゃる", "Back": "(respectful) to be,to come or to go", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "植える", "Back": "to plant,to grow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "うかがう", "Back": "to visit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "受付", "Back": "receipt", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "受ける", "Back": "to take a lesson or test", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "動く", "Back": "to move", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "うそ", "Back": "a lie", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "うち", "Back": "within", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "打つ", "Back": "to hit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "美しい", "Back": "beautiful", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "写す", "Back": "to copy or photograph", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "移る", "Back": "to move house or transfer", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "腕", "Back": "arm", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "うまい", "Back": "delicious", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "裏", "Back": "reverse side", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "売り場", "Back": "place where things are sold", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "うれしい", "Back": "glad", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "うん", "Back": "(informal) yes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "運転", "Back": "to drive", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "運転手", "Back": "driver", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "運動", "Back": "to exercise", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "エスカレーター", "Back": "escalator", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "枝", "Back": "branch, twig", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "選ぶ", "Back": "to choose", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "遠慮", "Back": "to be reserved, to be restrained", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おいでになる", "Back": "(respectful) to be", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お祝い", "Back": "congratulation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "オートバイ", "Back": "motorcycle", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おかげ", "Back": "owing to", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おかしい", "Back": "strange or funny", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "億", "Back": "one hundred million", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "屋上", "Back": "rooftop", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "贈り物", "Back": "gift", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "送る", "Back": "to send", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "遅れる", "Back": "to be late", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "起す", "Back": "to wake", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "行う", "Back": "to do", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "怒る", "Back": "to get angry,to be angry", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "押し入れ", "Back": "closet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お嬢さん", "Back": "young lady", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お宅", "Back": "(polite) your house", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "落る", "Back": "to fall or drop", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おっしゃる", "Back": "(respectful) to say", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "夫", "Back": "husband", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おつり", "Back": "change from purchase, balance", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "音", "Back": "sound,note", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "落す", "Back": "to drop", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "踊り", "Back": "a dance", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "踊る", "Back": "to dance", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "驚く", "Back": "to be surprised", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お祭り", "Back": "festival", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お見舞い", "Back": "calling on someone who is ill,enquiry", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お土産", "Back": "souvenir", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "思い出す", "Back": "to remember", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "思う", "Back": "to think,to feel", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おもちゃ", "Back": "toy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "表", "Back": "the front", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "親", "Back": "parents", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "下りる", "Back": "to get off", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "折る", "Back": "to break or to fold", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お礼", "Back": "expression of gratitude", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "折れる", "Back": "to break or be folded", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "終わり", "Back": "the end", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "カーテン", "Back": "curtain", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "海岸", "Back": "coast", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "会議", "Back": "meeting", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "会議室", "Back": "meeting room", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "会場", "Back": "assembly hall or meeting place", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "会話", "Back": "conversation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "帰り", "Back": "return", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "変える", "Back": "to change", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "科学", "Back": "science", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "鏡", "Back": "mirror", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "掛ける", "Back": "to hang something", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "飾る", "Back": "to decorate", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "火事", "Back": "fire", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ガス", "Back": "petrol", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ガソリン", "Back": "petrol", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ガソリンスタンド", "Back": "petrol station", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "堅/硬/固い", "Back": "hard", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "形", "Back": "shape", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "片付ける", "Back": "to tidy up", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "課長", "Back": "section manager", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "勝つ", "Back": "to win", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "かっこう", "Back": "appearance", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "家内", "Back": "housewife", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "悲しい", "Back": "sad", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "必ず", "Back": "certainly,necessarily", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お・金持ち", "Back": "rich man", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "彼女", "Back": "she,girlfriend", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "壁", "Back": "wall", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "かまう", "Back": "to mind", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "髪", "Back": "hair", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "噛む", "Back": "to bite,to chew", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "通う", "Back": "to commute", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ガラス", "Back": "a glass pane", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "彼", "Back": "he,boyfriend", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "彼ら", "Back": "they", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "乾く", "Back": "to get dry", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "代わり", "Back": "substitute,alternate", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "変わる", "Back": "to change", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "考える", "Back": "to consider", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "関係", "Back": "relationship", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "看護婦", "Back": "female nurse", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "簡単", "Back": "simple", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "気", "Back": "spirit,mood", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "機会", "Back": "opportunity", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "危険", "Back": "danger", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "聞こえる", "Back": "to be heard", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "汽車", "Back": "steam train", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "技術", "Back": "art,technology,skill", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "季節", "Back": "season", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "規則", "Back": "regulations", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "きっと", "Back": "surely", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "絹", "Back": "silk", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "厳しい", "Back": "strict", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "気分", "Back": "mood", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "決る", "Back": "to be decided", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "君", "Back": "(informal) You (used by men towards women)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "決める", "Back": "to decide", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "気持ち", "Back": "feeling,mood", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "着物", "Back": "kimono", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "客", "Back": "guest,customer", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "急", "Back": "urgent, steep", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "急行", "Back": "speedy, express", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "教育", "Back": "education", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "教会", "Back": "church", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "競争", "Back": "competition", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "興味", "Back": "an interest", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "近所", "Back": "neighbourhood", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "具合", "Back": "condition,health", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "空気", "Back": "air,atmosphere", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "空港", "Back": "airport", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "草", "Back": "grass", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "くださる", "Back": "(respectful) to give", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "首", "Back": "neck", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "雲", "Back": "cloud", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "比べる", "Back": "to compare", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "くれる", "Back": "to give", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "暮れる", "Back": "to get dark,to come to an end", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "毛", "Back": "hair or fur", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "計画", "Back": "to plan", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "経験", "Back": "to experience", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "経済", "Back": "finance,economy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "警察", "Back": "police", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ケーキ", "Back": "cake", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "けが・する", "Back": "to injure", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "景色", "Back": "scene,landscape", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "消しゴム", "Back": "eraser", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "下宿", "Back": "lodging", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "決して", "Back": "never", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "けれど/けれども", "Back": "however", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "原因", "Back": "cause,source", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "けんか・する", "Back": "to quarrel", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "研究", "Back": "research", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "研究室", "Back": "study room,laboratory", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "見物", "Back": "sightseeing", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "子", "Back": "child", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "こう", "Back": "this way", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "郊外", "Back": "outskirts", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "講義", "Back": "lecture", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "工業", "Back": "the manufacturing industry", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "高校", "Back": "high school", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "高校生", "Back": "high school student", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "工場", "Back": "factory", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "校長", "Back": "headmaster", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "交通", "Back": "traffic,transportation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "講堂", "Back": "auditorium", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "高等学校", "Back": "high school", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "公務員", "Back": "government worker", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "国際", "Back": "international", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "心", "Back": "core,heart", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "御主人", "Back": "(honorable) your husband", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "故障", "Back": "to break-down", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ご存じ", "Back": "knowing,acquaintance", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "答", "Back": "response", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ごちそう", "Back": "a feast", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "こと", "Back": "thing,matter", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "小鳥", "Back": "small bird", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "このあいだ", "Back": "the other day,recently", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "このごろ", "Back": "these days,nowadays", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "細かい", "Back": "small, fine", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ごみ", "Back": "rubbish", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "込む", "Back": "to be crowded", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "米", "Back": "uncooked rice", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ごらんになる", "Back": "(respectful) to see", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "これから", "Back": "after this", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "怖い", "Back": "frightening", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "壊す", "Back": "to break", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "壊れる", "Back": "to be broken", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "コンサート", "Back": "concert", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今度", "Back": "now,next time", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "コンピュータ/コンピューター", "Back": "computer", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今夜", "Back": "tonight", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "最近", "Back": "latest,nowadays", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "最後", "Back": "last,end", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "最初", "Back": "beginning,first", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "坂", "Back": "slope,hill", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "探す", "Back": "to look for", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "下る", "Back": "to get down,to descend", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "盛ん", "Back": "popularity,prosperous", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "下げる", "Back": "to hang,to lower,to move back", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "差し上げる", "Back": "(polite) to give", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "さっき", "Back": "some time ago", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "寂しい", "Back": "lonely", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "さ来月", "Back": "the month after next", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "さ来週", "Back": "the week after next", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "サラダ", "Back": "salad", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "騒ぐ", "Back": "to make noise,to be excited", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "触る", "Back": "to touch", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "産業", "Back": "industry", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "サンダル", "Back": "sandal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "サンドイッチ", "Back": "sandwich", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "残念", "Back": "disappointment", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "市", "Back": "city", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "字", "Back": "character", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "試合", "Back": "match,game", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "仕方", "Back": "method", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "しかる", "Back": "a particular", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "試験", "Back": "examination", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "事故", "Back": "accident", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "地震", "Back": "earthquake", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "時代", "Back": "era", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "下着", "Back": "underwear", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "支度", "Back": "to prepare", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "しっかり", "Back": "firmly,steadily", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "失敗", "Back": "failure,mistake", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "辞典", "Back": "dictionary", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "品物", "Back": "goods", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "しばらく", "Back": "little while", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "島", "Back": "island", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "市民", "Back": "citizen", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "事務所", "Back": "office", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "社会", "Back": "society,public", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "社長", "Back": "company president", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "じゃま", "Back": "hindrance,intrusion", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ジャム", "Back": "jam", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "自由", "Back": "freedom", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "習慣", "Back": "custom,manners", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "住所", "Back": "an address,a residence", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "柔道", "Back": "judo", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "十分", "Back": "enough", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "出席", "Back": "to attend", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "出発", "Back": "to depart", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "趣味", "Back": "hobby", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "準備", "Back": "to prepare", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "紹介", "Back": "introduction", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "小学校", "Back": "elementary school", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "小説", "Back": "novel", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "招待", "Back": "to invite", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "承知", "Back": "to consent", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "将来", "Back": "future,prospects", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "食事", "Back": "to have a meal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "食料品", "Back": "groceries", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "女性", "Back": "woman", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "知らせる", "Back": "to notify", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "調べる", "Back": "to investigate", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "人口", "Back": "population", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "神社", "Back": "Shinto shrine", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "親切", "Back": "kindness", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "心配", "Back": "to worry", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "新聞社", "Back": "newspaper company", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "水泳", "Back": "swimming", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "水道", "Back": "water supply", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ずいぶん", "Back": "extremely", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "数学", "Back": "mathematics,arithmetic", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "スーツ", "Back": "suit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "スーツケース", "Back": "suitcase", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "過ぎる", "Back": "to exceed", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "すく", "Back": "to become empty", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "スクリーン", "Back": "screen", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "凄い", "Back": "terrific", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "進む", "Back": "to make progress", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "すっかり", "Back": "completely", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "すっと", "Back": "straight,all of a sudden", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ステーキ", "Back": "steak", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "捨てる", "Back": "to throw away", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ステレオ", "Back": "stereo", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "砂", "Back": "sand", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "すばらしい", "Back": "wonderful", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "滑る", "Back": "to slide,to slip", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "隅", "Back": "corner,nook", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "済む", "Back": "to finish", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "すり", "Back": "pickpocket", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "すると", "Back": "then", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "生活", "Back": "to live", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "生産", "Back": "to produce", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "政治", "Back": "politics,government", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "西洋", "Back": "western countries", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "世界", "Back": "the world", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "席", "Back": "seat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "説明", "Back": "explanation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "背中", "Back": "back of the body", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "世話", "Back": "to look after", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ぜひ", "Back": "without fail", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "線", "Back": "line", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ぜんぜん", "Back": "not entirely (used in a negative sentence)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "戦争", "Back": "war", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "先輩", "Back": "senior", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そう", "Back": "really", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "相談", "Back": "to discuss", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "育てる", "Back": "to rear,to bring up", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "卒業", "Back": "graduation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "祖父", "Back": "grandfather", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "祖母", "Back": "grandmother", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ソフト", "Back": "soft", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "それで", "Back": "because of that", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "それに", "Back": "moreover", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "それほど", "Back": "to that extent", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そろそろ", "Back": "gradually,soon", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そんな", "Back": "that sort of", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そんなに", "Back": "so much,like that", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "退院", "Back": "to leave hospital", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大学生", "Back": "university student", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大事", "Back": "important,valuable,serious matter", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大体", "Back": "generally", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "たいてい", "Back": "usually", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "タイプ", "Back": "type,style", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大分", "Back": "greatly", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "台風", "Back": "typhoon", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "倒れる", "Back": "to break down", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "だから", "Back": "so,therefore", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "確か", "Back": "definite", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "足す", "Back": "to add a number", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "訪ねる", "Back": "to visit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "尋ねる", "Back": "to ask", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "正しい", "Back": "correct", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "畳", "Back": "Japanese straw mat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "立てる", "Back": "to stand something up", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "建てる", "Back": "to build", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "例えば", "Back": "for example", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "棚", "Back": "shelves", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "楽しみ", "Back": "joy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "楽む", "Back": "to enjoy oneself", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "たまに", "Back": "occasionally", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "為", "Back": "in order to", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "だめ", "Back": "no good", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "足りる", "Back": "to be enough", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "男性", "Back": "male", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "暖房", "Back": "heating", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "血", "Back": "blood", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "チェック・する", "Back": "to check", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "力", "Back": "strength,power", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ちっとも", "Back": "not at all (used with a negative verb)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ちゃん", "Back": "suffix for familiar female person", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "注意", "Back": "caution", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "中学校", "Back": "junior high school,middle school", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "注射", "Back": "injection", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "駐車場", "Back": "parking lot", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "地理", "Back": "geography", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "捕まえる", "Back": "to seize", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "つき", "Back": "moon", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "付く", "Back": "to be attached", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "漬ける", "Back": "to soak,to pickle", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "都合", "Back": "circumstances,convenience", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "伝える", "Back": "to report", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "続く", "Back": "to be continued", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "続ける", "Back": "to continue", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "包む", "Back": "to wrap", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "妻", "Back": "(humble) wife", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "つもり", "Back": "intention", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "釣る", "Back": "to fish", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "連れる", "Back": "to lead", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "丁寧", "Back": "polite", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "テキスト", "Back": "text,text book", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "適当", "Back": "suitability", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "できるだけ", "Back": "as much as possible", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "手伝う", "Back": "to assist", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "テニス", "Back": "tennis", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "手袋", "Back": "glove", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "寺", "Back": "temple", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "点", "Back": "point,dot", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "店員", "Back": "shop assistant", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "天気予報", "Back": "weather forecast", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "電灯", "Back": "electric light", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "電報", "Back": "telegram", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "展覧会", "Back": "exhibition", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "都", "Back": "metropolitan", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "道具", "Back": "tool,means", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "とうとう", "Back": "finally, after all", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "動物園", "Back": "zoo", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "遠く", "Back": "distant", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "通る", "Back": "to go through", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "特に", "Back": "particularly,especially", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "特別", "Back": "special", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "とこや", "Back": "barber", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "途中", "Back": "on the way", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "特急", "Back": "limited express train (faster than an express train)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "届ける", "Back": "to reach", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "泊まる", "Back": "to lodge at", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "止める", "Back": "to stop something", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "取り替える", "Back": "to exchange", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "泥棒", "Back": "thief", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どんどん", "Back": "more and more", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "直す", "Back": "to fix,to repair", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "直る", "Back": "to be fixed,to be repaired", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "治る", "Back": "to be cured,to heal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "中々", "Back": "considerably", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "泣く", "Back": "to weep", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "無くなる", "Back": "to disappear,to get lost", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "亡くなる", "Back": "to die", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "投げる", "Back": "to throw or cast away", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "なさる", "Back": "(respectful) to do", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "鳴る", "Back": "to sound", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "なるべく", "Back": "as much as possible", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "なるほど", "Back": "now I understand", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "慣れる", "Back": "to grow accustomed to", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "におい", "Back": "a smell", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "苦い", "Back": "bitter", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "二階建て", "Back": "two storied", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "逃げる", "Back": "to escape", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "日記", "Back": "journal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "入院", "Back": "to hospitalise", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "入学", "Back": "to enter school or university", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "似る", "Back": "to be similar", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "人形", "Back": "doll, figure", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "盗む", "Back": "to steal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "塗る", "Back": "to paint,to plaster", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ぬれる", "Back": "to get wet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ねだん", "Back": "price", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "熱", "Back": "fever", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ねっしん", "Back": "enthusiasm", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "寝坊", "Back": "sleeping in late", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "眠い", "Back": "sleepy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "眠る", "Back": "to sleep", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "残る", "Back": "to remain", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "のど", "Back": "throat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "乗り換える", "Back": "to change between buses or trains", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "乗り物", "Back": "vehicle", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "葉", "Back": "leaf", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "場合", "Back": "situation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "パート", "Back": "part time", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "倍", "Back": "double", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "拝見", "Back": "(humble) to look at", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "歯医者", "Back": "dentist", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "運ぶ", "Back": "to transport", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "始める", "Back": "to begin", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "場所", "Back": "location", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "はず", "Back": "it should be so", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "恥ずかしい", "Back": "embarrassed", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "パソコン", "Back": "personal computer", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "発音", "Back": "pronunciation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "はっきり", "Back": "clearly", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "花見", "Back": "cherry-blossom viewing", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "林", "Back": "woods,forester", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "払う", "Back": "to pay", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "番組", "Back": "television or radio program", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "反対", "Back": "opposition", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ハンドバッグ", "Back": "handbag　", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "日", "Back": "day, sun", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "火", "Back": "fire", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ピアノ", "Back": "piano", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "冷える", "Back": "to grow cold", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "光", "Back": "light", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "光る", "Back": "to shine,to glitter", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "引き出し", "Back": "drawer,drawing out", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "引き出す", "Back": "to withdraw", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ひげ", "Back": "beard", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "飛行場", "Back": "airport", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "久しぶり", "Back": "after a long time", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "美術館", "Back": "art gallery", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "非常に", "Back": "extremely", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "びっくり・する", "Back": "to be surprised", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "引っ越す", "Back": "to move house", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "必要", "Back": "necessary", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ひどい", "Back": "awful", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "開く", "Back": "to open an event", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ビル", "Back": "building or bill", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "昼間", "Back": "daytime,during the day", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "昼休み", "Back": "noon break", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "拾う", "Back": "to pick up,to gather", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ファックス", "Back": "fax", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "増える", "Back": "to increase", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "深い", "Back": "deep", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "複雑", "Back": "complexity,complication", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "復習", "Back": "revision", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "部長", "Back": "head of a section", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "普通", "Back": "usually, or a train that stops at every station", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ぶどう", "Back": "grapes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "太る", "Back": "to become fat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "布団", "Back": "Japanese bedding, futon", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "舟", "Back": "ship", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "不便", "Back": "inconvenience", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "踏む", "Back": "to step on", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "降り出す", "Back": "to start to rain", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "プレゼント", "Back": "present", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "文化", "Back": "culture", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "文学", "Back": "literature", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "文法", "Back": "grammar", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "別", "Back": "different", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ベル", "Back": "bell", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "変", "Back": "strange", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "返事", "Back": "reply", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "貿易", "Back": "trade", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "放送", "Back": "to broadcast", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "法律", "Back": "law", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "僕", "Back": "I (used by males)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "星", "Back": "star", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ほど", "Back": "extent", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ほとんど", "Back": "mostly", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ほめる", "Back": "to praise", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "翻訳", "Back": "translation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "参る", "Back": "(humble) to go,to come", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "負ける", "Back": "to lose", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "まじめ", "Back": "serious", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "まず", "Back": "first of all", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "または", "Back": "or,otherwise", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "間違える", "Back": "to make a mistake", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "間に合う", "Back": "to be in time for", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "周り", "Back": "surroundings", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "回る", "Back": "to go around", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "漫画", "Back": "comic", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "真中", "Back": "middle", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "見える", "Back": "to be in sight", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "湖", "Back": "lake", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "味噌", "Back": "bean paste", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "見つかる", "Back": "to be discovered", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "見つける", "Back": "to discover", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "皆", "Back": "everybody", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "港", "Back": "harbour", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "向かう", "Back": "to face", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "迎える", "Back": "to go out to meet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "昔", "Back": "olden days, former", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "虫", "Back": "insect", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "息子", "Back": "(humble) son", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "娘", "Back": "(humble) daughter", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "無理", "Back": "impossible", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "召し上がる", "Back": "(polite) to eat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "珍しい", "Back": "rare", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "申し上げる", "Back": "(humble) to say,to tell", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "申す", "Back": "(humble) to be called,to say", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "もうすぐ", "Back": "soon", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "もし", "Back": "if", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "もちろん", "Back": "of course", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "もっとも", "Back": "extremely", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "戻る", "Back": "to turn back", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "木綿", "Back": "cotton", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "もらう", "Back": "to receive", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "森", "Back": "forest", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "焼く", "Back": "to bake,to grill", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "約束", "Back": "promise", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "役に立つ", "Back": "to be helpful", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "焼ける", "Back": "to burn,to be roasted", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "優しい", "Back": "kind", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "痩せる", "Back": "to become thin", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "やっと", "Back": "at last", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "やはり/やっぱり", "Back": "as I thought,absolutely", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "止む", "Back": "to stop", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "柔らかい", "Back": "soft", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "湯", "Back": "hot water", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "輸出", "Back": "to export", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "輸入", "Back": "to import", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "指", "Back": "finger", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "指輪", "Back": "finger ring", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "夢", "Back": "dream", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "揺れる", "Back": "to shake,to sway", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "用", "Back": "use", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "用意", "Back": "preparation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "用事", "Back": "things to do", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "汚れる", "Back": "to get dirty", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "予習", "Back": "preparation for a lesson", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "予定", "Back": "arrangement", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "予約", "Back": "reservation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "寄る", "Back": "to visit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "喜ぶ", "Back": "to be delighted", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "よろしい", "Back": "(respectful) OK,all right", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "理由", "Back": "reason", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "利用", "Back": "utilization", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "両方", "Back": "both sides", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "旅館", "Back": "Japanese hotel", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "留守", "Back": "absence", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "冷房", "Back": "air conditioning", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "歴史", "Back": "history", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "レジ", "Back": "register", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "レポート/リポート", "Back": "report", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "連絡", "Back": "contact", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ワープロ", "Back": "word processor", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "沸かす", "Back": "to boil,to heat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "別れる", "Back": "to separate", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "沸く", "Back": "to boil, to grow hot,to get excited", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "訳", "Back": "meaning,reason", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "忘れ物", "Back": "lost article", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "笑う", "Back": "to laugh,to smile", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "割合", "Back": "rate,ratio,percentage", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "割れる", "Back": "to break", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "泳ぎ方", "Back": "way of swimming", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{}]
